I want to fly farther.
I want to fly to a wider world.
Kettle and Idol
Wait, wait, wait!
What the hell!
Isn't it too long to cut?
Oh, come on!
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
There's so much room, there's so much room.
Just a minute.
Question.
Okay, you two.
Charm!
Charming!
Yes, sir.
If it's a question and you write it like this, yes. Mr. Hayama, you are charming.
Charming.
I can't even say myself if I have charm,
But I think I do.
What is it? Certainly, I am loved by everyone, seniors and juniors alike.
What is it? You are an only child, right?
I am an only child.
Have you always been an only child?
People have always gathered around you and around you.
Wow. That's what I said.
When I was in elementary school, I was a cheerleader.
Cheerleader?
I won it with my charm.
There were about three kids who wanted to be the cheerleader, including me,
There were three of us.
Then we voted on it,
And we probably finished first.
Popular?
Popular, right?
No, I don't think I was popular with the romantic type,
But I think I was popular among friends.
I see. So everyone gathers around you.
Everyone gathers together,
When I was in junior high school, I had a lot of relative lessons and so on,
I see.
Because of this job.
I had a lot of relative work, so there were times when I couldn't do things like cleaning,
But then, I would usually say, "What? I would say, "You're not going to clean again, are you?
You're going to skip cleaning again?
But then, everyone would say, "Go ahead.
Is that true?
Yes! Really!
Everyone says, "Go see idols.
Do they tease you about going to see idols?
No, I'm not teased.
I was an idol in junior high school.
I see.
Do you have any more episodes where you benefited from your charm?
In that play.
I'm thankful that my co-stars
I'm grateful for that.
Every time I perform on various stages
and bought me a lot of things.
What a nice story.
Also, I've been doing something called "Harimakana" for a long time.
I've been doing something called Harimakana for a long time. I've been doing it for a long time.
All my co-stars use it.
What?
Your co-stars in that play...
What kind of place?
For example, when we make announcements.
I wonder if everyone will come to Harimakana.
They use the name Harimakana.
They love you.
That's right.
But that's important.
It's the power of humanity.
You guys probably haven't changed since the old days.
That's right. You haven't changed at all.
How about your charm?
For the fans?
To the fans?
You say that a lot. I do say that to them.
Yes, I do.
That's the point.
There is a difference between charm and mockery.
Oh! I heard that. There is a difference between charm and mockery.
Maybe what fans are looking for
more than charm, right?
This is a bit like idols.
Harima has been doing this for about 10 years now.
So no matter how charming and smiling he is
If you were to get shot in the face with a one-shot wrestling match, you'd go that way.
I see.
That's why, no matter how much he talks like this during the MC.
I'm going to say "Aa" during the MC. Even if I don't have a microphone.
Even if I'm saying "aah".
Is that right?
Yes, I do. If you say "aah"...
I think it's cute.
But I'm at the end, so I don't really get close to them.
That's why...
That's the mother, isn't it?
So, as I said, most of the bruised girls are in the center of the room.So, as I said, bruised girls tend to be in the center.
A girl with a good looks tends to be in the center.
They tend to be in the center.
So the number of idol fans is not the same as their charm.
It's different from charm.
It's different.
So I'm like, "I'm going to fill it from the people concerned.
Like a school idol.
I think they are school idols.
School idols, too.
And this too. Even though they are idols.
No, but it is.
That's why I got along with Wuhan and the others so easily.
Yes, that's the kind of charm.
The charm of parats.
Kettle and idol.
I'm often told that I have a strange obsession.
I'll prepare it after I'm done eating. I'll keep it short.
This show is about Sagara Rei-san
Sakka Kozo
Keisuke
Yuriya-chan
Aozura no Youni-san
We are grateful to all of them for their support. Thank you very much.